AARON JOHNSON

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER





347.786.0266



aaron@ajfs.me



www.ajfs.me



177-08 Sayres Ave Addisleigh Park, NY 11433

ABOUT ME

A multi-disciplinary pixel-perefectionist with a love for clean code, I bring a wealth of diverse experience to the table enabling me to hit the ground running on entry. I particularly excel in high-stakes environments where my contributions are essential toward both team and org KPIs.

EXPERIENCE

INTERACTIVE DESIGNER

POST STUDIOS 2019 - 2020

Using Photoshop, Illustrator & XD, I design mockups for digital interactive ad campaigns. Then, with HTML, CSS & JavaScript, I craft the experiences for both web & mobile.

CREATIVE MANAGER

TREMOR VIDEO 2014 - 2018

Oversaw the distribution of pre-production mockups & post-production campaigns to various members of the design team and offered design guidance as needed. Worked collaboratively with sales and ad ops depts. in educating clientele as to our product offering and platform capabilities. Additionally, supplied support for maximum transparency surrounding campaign goals and outcomes.

DESIGNER

TREMOR VIDEO 2013 - 2014

Designed and built custom advertising experiences using Photoshop, ActionScript & JavaScript. Handled all levels of development, from animation to interaction to custom reporting exposure.

EDUCATION

A.S., DIGITAL MEDIA COMMUNICATIONS KATHARINE GIBBS SCHOOL

2004 - 2006

Web major, focusing on design theory and and application through practical development. Acquired knowledge of Adobe CS, HTML, CSS & ActionScript. Graduated in the top 10 percen-

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT Lambda School

2019 - 2020

Continuing web development education, focusing on current technologies and best practices. Technologies include React.is for frontend development, Node.is (backend), Python (CS theory, data structures & algorithms) as well as Knex & PostgreSQL for query-building and database management.

SKILLS

HTML	
CSS	
JAVASCRIPT	
REACT	
NODE	
PYTHON	
POSTGRES	
GIT	

HOBBIES



Gaming

REFERENCES

Available upon request.







Fitness



